(Sheldon:)When she's upset,
she says "ack" and eats ice cream.
(Penny:)Um....
(Penny:)Ack.
And if you were a cat,
I would have brought you a lasagna.
(Penny:)Did Leonard send you over here?
(Sheldon:)No. We haven't spoken
since your abrupt departure last night...
(Sheldon:)...caused us to forfeit to Stuart
and his dastardly ringer, Wil Wheaton.
(Penny:)Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
(Sheldon:)Not too proud to admit
that I cried myself to sleep.
(Penny:)-Again, I'm sorry.
-Let me tell you...
(Sheldon:)...sleep did not come easily...
(Sheldon:)...with Leonard in the next room
singing along with Alanis Morissette.
(Penny:)-You're kidding.
-No.
(Sheldon:)Clearly another woman
in dire need of ice cream.
(Penny:)What part of this is supposed
to make me feel better?
(Sheldon:)The part where I tell you
I've engineered a rematch...
(Sheldon:)...with Stuart's team for tonight.
(Penny:)Oh, honey, I don't know. Things
are a little weird with Leonard right now.